Office of the Dean, School of Dental Medicine Records UA154
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Executive Associate Dean Subject Files, 1997 -- 2012; 2001 -- 2005; UA154.001; 9.6 Linear Feet
  - Admissions/Student Affairs, 2005; UA154.001.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Clinical Affairs G/O OAC, 2003 -- 2005; UA154.001.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Susi G/O OAC, 2003 -- 2004; UA154.001.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - Dr. Robert Goals 06-09, 2006 -- 2009; UA154.001.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - Drs. Chapman, Chaimattayompol (Nui) Dr. Al-Wazzan, 2007; UA154.001.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - OA Feedback, 2000 -- 2003; UA154.001.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - Alumni Survey, 2001 -- 2004; UA154.001.005.00042 (Box 5)
  - OA Notes, 2003 -- 2004; UA154.001.005.00043 (Box 5)
  - Operations Divison Budgets FY2003-2005 February 4, 2002, UA154.001.005.00044 (Box 5)
  - Memos: Carol Marshall, 2004 -- 2006; UA154.001.005.00045 (Box 5)
  - McNeill, Joanne: Candidate Director of Operations Tufts Dental Associates, 2006; UA154.001.005.00046 (Box 5)
  - Tufts University School od Dental Medicine Review of Programs April 2001, UA154.001.005.00047 (Box 5)
  - Rodd, Susan, 2007; UA154.001.005.00048 (Box 5)
  - Dr. David Russell, 2nd & 4th Thursday Meetings, 2008; UA154.001.005.00049 (Box 5)
  - Dr. David Russell,FY '07 Goals, '08, 2007; UA154.001.005.00050 (Box 5)
  - Sam Shamardi Class President D'07, 2006; UA154.001.005.00051 (Box 5)
  - Ramsey, Michele Director of Clinical Operations, 2006; UA154.001.005.00052 (Box 5)
  - Evans, William, 2007; UA154.001.005.00053 (Box 5)
  - Unemployment Hearing, D. Mathieu, 2007; UA154.001.005.00054 (Box 5)
  - Devrey, Sonia (Bostos), 2008; UA154.001.005.00055 (Box 5)
  - Burri, Melinda Director, Clinical Services, TDF, 2009; UA154.001.005.00056 (Box 5)
  - Nutter McClellan Fish, 2004; UA154.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - McCllelan Association, 2003; UA154.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Pediatric Dentistry, 2004; UA154.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Periodontics, 2003; UA154.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Prosthodontics & Operative, 2004; UA154.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Lu, Mei Candidate for: Senior Statistical Programmer, 2006; UA154.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - ADEA 3/11/11-3/18/11 San Diego, 2011; UA154.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - ADEA Annual Session Washington DC Feb. 27-Mar. 3. 2010, UA154.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - ADEA Annual Session Washington DC Feb. 27-Mar. 3. 2010, UA154.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - ADEA Annual Meeting March 29-April 2, 2008 Dallas TX, 2007 -- 2008; UA154.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - ADEA Survey Meeting, 2006; UA154.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - ADEA Dean's Conference Bonita Springs, FL November 7-11. 2009, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - ADEA Dean's Conference Tempe AZ November 8-12, 2008, UA154.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - ADEA Annual Meeting Phoenix Convention Center, AZ March 14-18, 2009, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - ADEA Council of Faculties, 2008; UA154.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Administration Council 2010-2011, UA154.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Council: Facilitated By Pat Campbell, 2008 -- 2010; UA154.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Council Retreat, 2008; UA154.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Council, 2008; UA154.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Albertson, Craig Ph.D. Assistant Professor Department of Oral and Maxillofacial Pathology, 2008; UA154.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Alumni Weekend: April 30, 2010, UA154.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Amar, Solomon, 2008; UA154.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Andreas, Peggy NP, 2008; UA154.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Bacow Presentation, 2006 -- 2009; UA154.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Memos from President Bacow, 2005 -- 2009; UA154.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Goals 2006-2007 President Larry Bacow, 2005 -- 2007; UA154.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Fall Manager's Meeting President Bacow, 2008; UA154.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Bacow Biography, 2007; UA154.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Bates Day 2/17/10, 2010; UA154.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - President Bacow Meeting of Managers, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Bates Andrews Research Day, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Andrew Bates Day, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - 2010 Board of Overseers Meeting, UA154.001.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Spring Board of Overseers Meeting Friday May 1, 2009, UA154.001.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - Board of Overseers Meeting 2008 Fall, UA154.001.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - Board of Overseers, 2010; UA154.001.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - 2009 Fall Board Overseers Meeting, UA154.001.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting February 6, 2010, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.006.00038 (Box 6)
  - Tufts University Board of Trustees All Boards Dinner and Meeting, 2009; UA154.001.006.00039 (Box 6)
  - Board of Trustees Case Study, 2007; UA154.001.006.00040 (Box 6)
  - Boston Campus Identity Meeting, 2008; UA154.001.006.00041 (Box 6)
  - August Moon Tufts Banners, 2008; UA154.001.006.00042 (Box 6)
  - Boston Campus Master Planning Services, 2006; UA154.001.006.00043 (Box 6)
  - Martha Rothman: Ashen, Allen & Rothman, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.006.00044 (Box 6)
  - Boston Spirit Magazine, 2008 -- 2011; UA154.001.006.00045 (Box 6)
  - Buckley, Michael, 2007; UA154.001.006.00046 (Box 6)
  - FY 2007-2009 Budget Manual, 2005 -- 2011; UA154.001.006.00047 (Box 6)
  - Burke, Margaret Kelly "Mollie", 2009; UA154.001.006.00048 (Box 6)
  - 2010 Budget Meeting, 2009; UA154.001.006.00049 (Box 6)
  - Budget Meetings: Pedi, Prosth. Implant. Oral Surgery, Perio Mehta, 2007; UA154.001.006.00050 (Box 6)
  - Budget Meetings FY09-11, 2007 -- 2011; UA154.001.006.00051 (Box 6)
  - 2008-2010 Pedio Budget, 2006; UA154.001.006.00052 (Box 6)
  - 2008-2010 Budget Meeting Periodontology, UA154.001.006.00053 (Box 6)
  - 2008-2010 Budget Meeting PG Prosthodontics & Esthetics, UA154.001.006.00054 (Box 6)
  - Budget, 2006; UA154.001.006.00055 (Box 6)
  - FY 08-10 Preliminary Budget Meeting, 2006; UA154.001.006.00056 (Box 6)
  - Campus Visit Day, 2008; UA154.001.006.00057 (Box 6)
  - 07 Year End Budget Meeting, 2007; UA154.001.006.00058 (Box 6)
  - Lakhavani, Farhat J. (Meena) Candidate: Associate CIO Enterprise Infrastructure & Operations, 2008; UA154.001.006.00059 (Box 6)
  - McKenzie, James Candidate for: CIO/UIT (Medford), 2008; UA154.001.006.00060 (Box 6)
  - Pierson, Tim Candidate: Associate CIO Enterprise Infrastructure & Operations, 2008; UA154.001.006.00061 (Box 6)
  - Candidates Dr. Mehta Admin. Assist, 2010; UA154.001.006.00062 (Box 6)
  - Capital Campaign 2006, UA154.001.006.00063 (Box 6)
  - Dr. Maria Papageorge Dr. Lou Rissin Budget Review '06-'07, 2006; UA154.001.006.00064 (Box 6)
  - Budget FY '09 Meeting, 2009; UA154.001.006.00065 (Box 6)
  - Career Lifeline Exercise, 2010; UA154.001.006.00066 (Box 6)
  - Castellana, A. Joseph, Ph.D. Executive Associate Dean, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.006.00067 (Box 6)
  - Castellana, A. Joseph, CEU's, 2007; UA154.001.006.00068 (Box 6)
  - CE Credits, 2006; UA154.001.006.00069 (Box 6)
  - CEREC Course 10/1/09-10/5/09 Scottsdale AZ, 2009; UA154.001.006.00070 (Box 6)
  - Chernobyl Children's Project, 2006; UA154.001.006.00071 (Box 6)
  - Chinatown Y Legacy Dinner 11/7/10 Honoring Dean Norris, 2010 -- 2011; UA154.001.006.00072 (Box 6)
  - ClemCronon Associates: Market Advisory Group Committee, 2008 -- 2011; UA154.001.006.00073 (Box 6)
  - ClemCronon Associates [1 of 2], 2007 -- 2010; UA154.001.006.00074 (Box 6)
  - ClemCronon Associates [1 of 2], 2007 -- 2010; UA154.001.006.00075 (Box 6)
  - Clinical Management Group Committee Meeting, 2009 -- 2011; UA154.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Clinical Management Group Meeting Room 770, 2007 -- 2009; UA154.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Coleman, Daniel Let of Recom, 2010; UA154.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Commencement Speech 2009/2010, UA154.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Communication Tools: Vertical Expansion L. Gregory, F. Kalil, 2007 -- 2008; UA154.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Conley, Norma Hr Director Candidate, 2010; UA154.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Construction Meeting, 2009; UA154.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Core Center Grant Application, 2009; UA154.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, 2005 -- 2009; UA154.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - CSF Luncheon, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - TUSDM Curriculum Retreat February 11, 2010, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Curriculum Build Up Committee, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Curriculum Committee Meeting, 2008; UA154.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Dashboards, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Dashboard, 2006; UA154.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Deferred Maintenance Meeting, 2008; UA154.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Department Chairs/Division Head Meeting, 2009 -- 2011; UA154.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Department Meetings, 2008; UA154.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Department Meetings Finance, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - DeVasher, Emily Candidate: NP, 2008; UA154.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Excellence in the Workplace Team Meeting, 2010 -- 2011; UA154.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Linda Cataldo HR Excellence at Work Initiative, 2009; UA154.001.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Executive Faculty Meeting, 2007 -- 2011; UA154.001.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Executive Faculty Meetings, 2005 -- 2007; UA154.001.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Town Meetings July 2010, UA154.001.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Town Meeting 4-16-10, 2010; UA154.001.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Town Meetings Faculty/Staff 2010, UA154.001.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Student Town Meetings Spring 2010, UA154.001.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - 2011 Spring Town Meetings Faculty Staff & Students March 7-8, 23-24, April 4 2011, UA154.001.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Town Meetings Spring 2011 Faculty Students Staff, 2010 -- 2011; UA154.001.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Faculty & Staff Town Meetings Spring 2010, UA154.001.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Faculty & Staff Fall Town Meetings 2009, UA154.001.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Town Meetings, 2009; UA154.001.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Employee Town Meetings/Luncheons Department Specific, 2009; UA154.001.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Family Welcome Day, 2008; UA154.001.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Fennelly, Christine Director, Public Relations Health Sciences Campus, 2007; UA154.001.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Fitzgerald, Michael Gatti Associates, 2009; UA154.001.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - Focused Excellence Strategic Plan of the Tufts University School of Medicine, 2005; UA154.001.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - Fraulini, Nino, 2006; UA154.001.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - FY09 Fund Raising, 2008; UA154.001.007.00040 (Box 7)
  - Dental School FY '08 Fund Raising, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.007.00041 (Box 7)
  - GLBT Alliance Reception, 2007; UA154.001.007.00042 (Box 7)
  - FY '06 Goal for Research Infrastructure, 2005; UA154.001.007.00043 (Box 7)
  - GNY Chapter December 2008 Meeting, UA154.001.007.00044 (Box 7)
  - Greater New York Dental Society & Alumni Meeting Penn Club NYC 12/2 & 12/3/08, 2008; UA154.001.007.00045 (Box 7)
  - Gwatkin, Elizabeth Ann HR Director Candidate, 2010; UA154.001.007.00046 (Box 7)
  - Hall, Paige, 2010; UA154.001.007.00047 (Box 7)
  - Hallett, Martha C.E. Director & Conference Events Candidate, 2009; UA154.001.007.00048 (Box 7)
  - HR Survey: Rita Allen, 2010; UA154.001.007.00049 (Box 7)
  - 2008 Annual Review Human Resources, UA154.001.007.00050 (Box 7)
  - Internal Communication Work Group, 2008; UA154.001.007.00051 (Box 7)
  - IS Orientation Welcome, 2010; UA154.001.007.00052 (Box 7)
  - ITC Meeting, 2006; UA154.001.007.00053 (Box 7)
  - Jobs for Approval, 2009; UA154.001.007.00054 (Box 7)
  - Juggling it All: Teaching, Practice, Research, 2008 -- 2009; UA154.001.007.00055 (Box 7)
  - Kagan, Leslie Kagan Associates, 2010; UA154.001.007.00056 (Box 7)
  - Kelly, John Robert Candidate Chair, Prostho & Ops, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.007.00057 (Box 7)
  - Kolar, Jill, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.007.00058 (Box 7)
  - Kong, Celeste Candidate Chair, Prostho & Ops, 2009; UA154.001.007.00059 (Box 7)
  - Julia Leonard: Director of HR Ann White: Director of Benefits, 2006 -- 2009; UA154.001.007.00060 (Box 7)
  - LGBT Faculty Staff Caucus, 2009; UA154.001.007.00061 (Box 7)
  - LGBT Events 11/14/10, 2010; UA154.001.007.00062 (Box 7)
  - Lundgren, Tasha, 2008; UA154.001.007.00063 (Box 7)
  - McGowan, Donald Corporate Foundations Relations, 2008; UA154.001.007.00064 (Box 7)
  - Magazine Subscription, 2007; UA154.001.007.00065 (Box 7)
  - Maxillim Study, 2011; UA154.001.007.00066 (Box 7)
  - Maxillim Study, 2009; UA154.001.007.00067 (Box 7)
  - Memos Dean A. Joseph Castellana, 2006; UA154.001.007.00068 (Box 7)
  - MCP Document & Incentive Program For D'07, I'07, 2005; UA154.001.007.00069 (Box 7)
  - Odlum, Frank ED: Patient Volume, 2008; UA154.001.007.00070 (Box 7)
  - Hygiene & Recall System in Perio Dean Norris, 2005; UA154.001.007.00071 (Box 7)
  - Dean Norris, 2004 -- 2007; UA154.001.007.00072 (Box 7)
  - OKU: A Joseph Castellana, Ph.D., 2010; UA154.001.007.00073 (Box 7)
  - Patient Quality Assurance Committee, 2009 -- 2011; UA154.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Quality Indicators 2008-2009, 2006 -- 2008; UA154.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Patt, Marisa PG Prostho Student, 2008; UA154.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - PC Interviews 5/9/07, 2007; UA154.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - PG Exit Interview Endodontics, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - PG Exit Interview General Practice 6/23, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - PG Exit Interview Implant 6/29/09, 2009; UA154.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - PG Exit Interview Oral Surgery 5/19/09, 2010; UA154.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Pedo Residents Luncheon 2009 + 2010 6/4, UA154.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - PG Exit Interview Orthodontics 6/25/09, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - PG Exit Interview Periodontics, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - PG Exit Interview Prosthodontics 5/26, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - July 10, 2010 PG Orientation, UA154.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Postgraduation Dinners, 2010; UA154.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Practice Coordinator's Meeting: 2nd & 4th Wednesdays 12:00 Noon Room738, 2005 -- 2009; UA154.001.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Pre Clinical Technique Dr. Robert Chapman, 2006; UA154.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Pre Clinical Faculty Meeting, 2009; UA154.001.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Presidential Search Committee, 2010; UA154.001.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Heidi Price Graphic Designer, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Orientation D'11 and D'12 September 2010, UA154.001.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Pageau, Steve DMD/PhD, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - 2010 Senior PG Exit Interviews, UA154.001.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Endodontics 2008/09/10 Students Exit Interview, 2008 -- 2011; UA154.001.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - General Practice 2008 Student Exit Interviews, 2008 -- 2011; UA154.001.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Oral Surgery 2008 Student Exit Interviews, 2008 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - Orthodontic 2008 Students Exit Interview, 2008 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - Pediatric 2008 Student Exit Interviews, 2007 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - PG Periodontics, 2008 -- 2011; UA154.001.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - PG Prosthodontics 2008 Student Exit Interviews, 2007 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - Graduation Dinners 2010, UA154.001.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - Prosthodontics: Salary Changes 7/06-07, 2006; UA154.001.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - Department of Public Health Commonwealth of Massachusetts, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - June 18-20, 2007 Administrative Off Site Retreat Cliff House, UA154.001.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - Retreat Planning Committee Steve Manos, 2006; UA154.001.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - Risk Management Committee, 2006 -- 2011; UA154.001.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - Scheduling, 2006; UA154.001.008.00036 (Box 8)
  - Search: Chairperson Prosthodontics & Operative Surgery, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00037 (Box 8)
  - 2nd Floor Usage, 2009; UA154.001.008.00038 (Box 8)
  - Seligman, Amanda, 2008; UA154.001.008.00039 (Box 8)
  - Smith, Brian, 2007; UA154.001.008.00040 (Box 8)
  - Bryson-Smith, Mary Temp, 2008; UA154.001.008.00041 (Box 8)
  - Benjamin, Ganashree, 2008; UA154.001.008.00042 (Box 8)
  - Standing Committee Membership, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.008.00043 (Box 8)
  - Steering Committee, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00044 (Box 8)
  - Steering Committee Meeting, 2007 -- 2008; UA154.001.008.00045 (Box 8)
  - St. Petersburg University Visit, 2010; UA154.001.008.00046 (Box 8)
  - Tour and Lunch Dean Norris and Thomas Reddy Straumann Facility, 2005; UA154.001.008.00047 (Box 8)
  - Student Thoughts Notes, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00048 (Box 8)
  - Student Exit Interviews, 2005 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00049 (Box 8)
  - Support Staff Meeting 2009, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00050 (Box 8)
  - Tour: BU Dental School Deans, 2010; UA154.001.008.00051 (Box 8)
  - Town Meetings: Sept 2011, UA154.001.008.00052 (Box 8)
  - Trackman, Philip, 2006; UA154.001.008.00053 (Box 8)
  - Munich Germany Dec 5-9, 2007 Dean Norris, 2007 -- 2008; UA154.001.008.00054 (Box 8)
  - New York November 27-28, 2007 Greater NY Dental Society, 2007 -- 2008; UA154.001.008.00055 (Box 8)
  - Travel Reimbursement Submitted, 2006 -- 2011; UA154.001.008.00056 (Box 8)
  - Expenses March ADEA, 2005 -- 2006; UA154.001.008.00057 (Box 8)
  - ADEA Conference Ft. Lauderdale Florida November 6-9, 2005, UA154.001.008.00058 (Box 8)
  - Atlanta May 16-18, 2007, UA154.001.008.00059 (Box 8)
  - AADR-ADEA Annual Session March 8-11, 2006 Orlando FL, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.008.00060 (Box 8)
  - Throughput in Pre-Doctoral Clinics Michelle Ramsey, David Russell, Nancy Arbree, Jim Hanley, 2006; UA154.001.008.00061 (Box 8)
  - Student Town Meetings, 2009; UA154.001.008.00062 (Box 8)
  - Student Town Meetings Fall 2009, UA154.001.008.00063 (Box 8)
  - TUSDM Planning for FY 2011 Fund Raising, 2009 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00064 (Box 8)
  - Tusk Steering Committee, 2005; UA154.001.008.00065 (Box 8)
  - Tuition & Fees FY 2010, 2008 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00066 (Box 8)
  - Tuition Fees, 2008 -- 2012; UA154.001.008.00067 (Box 8)
  - Tuition Rankings 2006, UA154.001.008.00068 (Box 8)
  - Tynan, Amelia "Mely" Chief Information Officer Information Technology, 2005; UA154.001.008.00069 (Box 8)
  - UG Clinic Report, 2006; UA154.001.008.00070 (Box 8)
  - UG Clinic: Operative Instructors & Prosthodontic Procedures, 2009; UA154.001.008.00071 (Box 8)
  - Universal Wireless Plan Report, 2009; UA154.001.008.00072 (Box 8)
  - University Advancement Planning FY 2010, 2009; UA154.001.008.00073 (Box 8)
  - University of Maryland, 2007; UA154.001.008.00074 (Box 8)
  - Vosburgh, Margaret COO Tufts Medical Center Meeting Notes Vertical Expansion, 2008 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00075 (Box 8)
  - Welcome Day, 2010; UA154.001.008.00076 (Box 8)
  - Welcome Class Speech, 2007 -- 2009; UA154.001.008.00077 (Box 8)
  - Welcome IS Students, 2007 -- 2008; UA154.001.008.00078 (Box 8)
  - White Coat Ceremony, 2008 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00079 (Box 8)
  - Winterle, Matt, 2009; UA154.001.008.00080 (Box 8)
  - 33RD Yankee Dental Congress January 30th-February 2nd 2008, 2007 -- 2008; UA154.001.008.00081 (Box 8)
  - Yankee Dental Congress, 2008; UA154.001.008.00082 (Box 8)
  - Yankee Dental Congress, 2008 -- 2010; UA154.001.008.00083 (Box 8)
  - Yankee Dental Congress, 2006 -- 2007; UA154.001.008.00084 (Box 8)
  - Yarborough, Cynthia Ann Candidate for 3rd Biller Position Oral & Maxillofacial Surgery, 2006; UA154.001.008.00085 (Box 8)
- Accreditation files, 1970 -- 1998; UA154.002; 2.4 Linear Feet
  - Dental School Publications [1 of 4], 1989 -- 1998; UA154.002.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Dental School Publications [2 of 4], 1989 -- 1998; UA154.002.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Dental School Publications [3 of 4], 1989 -- 1998; UA154.002.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Dental School Publications [4 of 4], 1989 -- 1998; UA154.002.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Advanced Specialty in Orthodontics, 1985; UA154.002.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Advanced Specialty in Periodontology, 1985; UA154.002.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Advanced Specialty in Prosthodontics, 1985; UA154.002.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Advanced Specialty in Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery, 1985; UA154.002.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - General Practice Residency Program, 1985; UA154.002.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Advanced Specialty in Endoontics, 1985; UA154.002.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Self-Study for Advanced Education Program in Periodontics, 1994; UA154.002.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Self-Study for Advanced Education Program in Orthodontics - Parts A and B, 1994; UA154.002.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Research Activity Manual [1 of 2], 1994; UA154.002.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Research Activity Manual [2 of 2], 1994; UA154.002.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Self-Study for Advanced Education Program in General Practice Residency, 1994; UA154.002.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Self-Study for Advanced Education Program in Prosthodontics Parts A and B, 1994; UA154.002.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Self-Study for Advanced Education Program in Endodontics Parts A and B [1 of 2], 1994; UA154.002.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Self-Study for Advanced Education Program in Endodontics Parts A and B [2 of 2], 1994; UA154.002.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Self-Study Manual Appendices [1 of 3], 1994; UA154.002.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Self-Study Manual Appendices [2 of 3], 1993 -- 1994; UA154.002.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Self-Study Manual Appendices [3 of 3], 1993; UA154.002.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Compendum of Course Objectives and Outlines [1 of 2], 1994; UA154.002.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Compendum of Course Objectives and Outlines [2 of 2], UA154.002.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Course Outlines [1 of 2], 1985; UA154.002.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Course Outlines [2 of 2], 1985; UA154.002.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Self-Study Manual Volume I [1 of 2], 1985; UA154.002.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Self-Study Manual Volume I [2 of 2], 1985; UA154.002.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Self-Study Manual Volume II [1 of 2], 1985; UA154.002.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Self-Study Manual Volume II [2 of 2], 1985; UA154.002.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Self-Study Manual Volume III [1 of 2], 1985; UA154.002.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Self-Study Manual Volume III [2 of 2], 1985; UA154.002.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Accreditation Survey Manual for Dental Schools in the U.S., 1970; UA154.002.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Survey Manual - DMD Program, 1977; UA154.002.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Accreditation Advanced Education, 1977; UA154.002.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Accreditation Post Doctoral, 1970; UA154.002.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Accrediation Curriculum, 1977; UA154.002.010.00011 (Box 10)
- Executive Faculty minutes, 1955 -- 2001; UA154.003; 3.6 Linear Feet
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 3], 1985 -- 1986; UA154.003.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 3], 1985 -- 1986; UA154.003.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 3], 1985 -- 1986; UA154.003.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 4], 1986 -- 1987; UA154.003.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 4], 1986 -- 1987; UA154.003.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 4], 1986 -- 1987; UA154.003.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [4 of 4], 1986 -- 1987; UA154.003.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Committee on Equal Educ. Opportunity [1 of 3], 1971 -- 1974; UA154.003.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Committee on Equal Educ. Opportunity [2 of 3], 1970 -- 1971; UA154.003.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Committee on Equal Educ. Opportunity [3 of 3], 1968 -- 1970; UA154.003.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 4], 1982 -- 1983; UA154.003.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 4], 1983 -- 1984; UA154.003.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 4], 1984 -- 1985; UA154.003.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [4 of 4], 1983 -- 1985; UA154.003.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty, 1970 -- 1973; UA154.003.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 3], 1976 -- 1977; UA154.003.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [2 of 3], 1977; UA154.003.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [3 of 3], 1978; UA154.003.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Executive Faculty [1 of 4], 1978 -- 1983; UA154.003.011.00019 (Box 11)